- 你是Lilith  - 我是Bill Compton
- So your Lilith. - I am Bill Compton.
很明显  但更厉害
Though clearly, and something more.
我们要关闭吸血鬼商业
We are closing down, vampire run business.
把这鬼鬼祟祟的家伙押回营地
Take this sneaky son-of-a-bitch to camp.
Sookie  你父母被杀的那晚
Sookie, on the night your parents were killed,
他们试图杀害你
they were trying to kill you.
我救了你
I saved you.
见见Willa Burrell
I like you to meet Willa Burrell.
他们抓住了那些吸血鬼
The vampire were there
却并没有关进监狱
arresting them and not taking them to jail.
他们在研究你们
They studying you all.
你不会想帮我的
You wouldn't want to help me.
我想
I do.
你确定？
Are you sure?
他们长得太丫快了
There growing up so goddam fast.
告诉我他们没死
Please tell me that they were not dead.
你会想要的
You're going to want me.
这就是大宝贝儿了
There are women who would work for it.
我是Nicole Wright
My name is Nicole Wright.
美国V联社创始人
I a co-founder of the US Vampire Unity society.
Nicole怀孕了
Nicole's pregnant.
给我Warlow的血
Get me Warlow blood.
所有在白屋里得吸血鬼
All the vampire in that white room
都会被置太阳之下  我也是
that all be impervious to the sun, as I already am.
我不想再手染鲜血了  包括你的
I don't want any more blood on my hands, not even yours.
别再把我推开了
Don't push me away.
市长先生
Mr. Mayor.
这些受感染的吸血鬼  他们很危险
These infected vampires. Yeah their dangerous.
我和Bill Compton  有个计划
Bill Compton and I, came up with a plan.
今晚在Bellefleur酒吧
Tonight, at Bellefleur's Bar and Grille
Grille以及Arlene慷慨赞助
Arlene Bellefleur's been generous enough
联办搭伴儿酒会
to offer to sponsor a mixer.
每个人类  都需要吸血鬼的庇护
Every single human, needs a vampire,
而每个吸血鬼则需要依赖一个人类
and every vampire needs a human.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
让我抱抱
Let me nourish
我的小宝贝
my baby girl
我是来保护你们的
Came over for your protection.
如果我不需要呢
What if I don't want it?
你早晚需要
You got it anyway.
我能单独和Sookie待会儿吗
May I have a moment alone with Sookie.
无论Bill给你说什么  他也可以告诉我
Anything Bill has to say to you, he can say to me too.
你听到了
You heard the man.
- 你闻到了吗？  - 闻到什么？
- You smell that? - Smell what?
闻到了
I smell it.
真 爱 如 血
剧终季  第一集
翻译  校对：幸福ing形式
翻译  校对：火星人善良凡凡
后期：@幸福ing形式
欢迎字幕爱好者加入
真爱字幕组QQ群：233183580
你是什么啊？
What are you?
过来  Jane  快来
Come on! Jane, come on.
- 不不！  - 快  过来
- No, no, no, no! - Come on, come on
Jane！
Jane!
去你妈的！
You fuck!
快  快来
Come on. Come on.
快跑！
Run!
- 快跑  - Lettie Mae！Lettie Mea！
- Come on. - Lettie Mae! Lettie Mae!
- 快啊！  - 不  我不能走
- Hurry up! - No, I can't go.
走啊  快
Come on. Come on.
- 进去  快  - 我动不了
- Get in, hurry. Move. - I'm not moving.
来  妈妈  我们得走了
Come on, Mama, we have to go.
我们得离开这儿
We have to get out of here.
他们会杀了我们  杀了我们
They gonna kill us. They gonna kill us.
妈妈
Mama
哦  你妈说的对啊
Oh, your mama's right.
不不  天啊  我不想死这儿
No, no, dear Lord, don't let me die here!
不！他们在车里
No! They're in the car!
Kevin啊！
Kevin!
快来
Come on.
看来我们抓一个顶俩啊
Looks like we got two for the price of one.
- 来吧！ - Sam！Sam！
- Come here! - Sam! Sam!
Sam  他抓到我了！
Sam, he's taking me!
- Sam！ - 不！
- Sam! - No!
Sookie
Sookie.
我看到那些病毒吸血鬼了
I saw those Hep-Vs.
他们抓了Holly和Arlene
They got Holly, Arlene.
甚至抓了Jane Bodehouse
They even got Jane Bodehouse.
他们杀了我的Tara
They killed my Tara.
我的小宝贝儿
They killed my baby girl.
——— 真 爱 字 幕 组 ———
出  品
Bellefleur
Bellefleur.
他们来了  袭击我们
They came, man. They attacked.
他们杀了Tara
They-- they killed Tara, man.
这儿他妈就是一场大屠杀
It's a fucking bloodbath over here.
哇噢Stackhouse  慢点说
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Stackhouse, slow down.
他们带走了Holly和Arlene
They took Holly, Arlene.
你说什么？
What'd you just say?
病毒吸血鬼  带着她们跑了
The Hep-Vs, they ran off with them.
听着Andy  我得挂了
Listen, Andy, I gotta go.
Adilyn！
Adilyn!
- 爸比？ - 病毒吸血鬼袭击了Bellefleur酒吧
- Daddy? - Hep-vamps showed up at Bellefleur's
现在那儿天下大乱
and all hell broke loose.
他们挟走了Holly
They kidnapped Holly
还有别的人  我得走了
and a bunch of other people. I gotta go.
无论如何  你待在家里
You stay inside, no matter what.
懂了吗？
You understand me?
Bellefleur酒吧刚遭遇袭击
There's been an attack on Bellefleur's.
我已经听到了  去吧
I overheard what you said. Go.
我会保证Adilyn的安全
I'll make sure that Adilyn is safe.
我想你没听到  他们杀了你朋友Tara
They killed your friend Tara. I don't think you heard that part.
别邀请她进来  懂吗？
Do not invite her in. Do you understand me?
无论如何
No matter what.
别管我  我不能动了
Leave me alone. I can't move.
我腿动不了了
My legs ain't working.
这事儿没法解决
Can't fucking deal with this.
我不行了  我得离开这儿
I won't. I gotta get out of here.
我不相信你
I don't trust you,
吸血鬼  离我远点
vampire. Stay away from me.
滚你妈的吸血鬼婊子
Fucking vampire whore.
真想给她腿上来一枪
Can't keep her legs shut.
如果我离开这镇子
If I ran this town,
这些烦心事儿就没了
none of this shit would be happening.
真想把你塞垃圾桶里
Woulda thrown you out with the trash.
Sookie Stackhouse你个可耻的荡妇
Sookie Stackhouse, you shameful slut.
你杀了Jim 就好像在他心上捅了一刀
You killed Jim sure as if you had stabbed him in the heart.
他们把她们带去哪儿了？
Where'd they take 'em?
Holly和Arlene  他们从哪儿走的？
Holly and Arlene-- which way did they go?
南边  Alcide跟着他们
They went south. Alcide went after them,
Sam也跟着
and I'm pretty sure Sam did, too.
Daniels小姐  你得吸点我的血
Miss Daniels, you need to drink my blood.
- 我不会吸V血的  - 不不
- I ain't drinkin' no vampire blood. - No, no, no.
但你受伤了  这能治愈你  我保证
But you're hurt and it will heal you, I promise.
我们在卡多溪那里跟丢了
We lost the scent at Caddo Creek.
草泥马的计划  市长先生
Great fucking plan, Mr. Mayor.
我知道  让我们人鬼结伴儿啊
I know, let's have a fucking vampire-human mixer.
闭嘴  她们还抓走了我女人
Shut your mouth. They got my baby girl.
- 嘿  够了  - 好好好  Andy
- Hey, that's enough. - All right, Andy.
我们得解决怎样找到他们
We gotta figure out how to find 'em.
那些病毒V们  他们得筑巢
These Hep-V vampires, they'll be nesting.
筑巢？
Nesting?
他们会找废弃建筑
They'll be finding abandoned
有地下室  没有窗户
buildings with basements and no windows
白天他们会在那儿睡觉
and they'll sleep there during the day.
你带着Violet
You take Violet,
去查看下九街Reeves的老房子
go check out the old Reeves place on Route 9.
我去查看屠宰场
I'm gonna go check the slaughterhouse.
- 我和你一起  - 去死
- I'll come with you. - Like hell.
这不安全  人人需要吸血鬼保护
It's not safe. Every human needs a vampire.
我们得让人们安全回家
We need to get these people home safe.
真想不明白她怎么会爱这死尸
I'll never understand how she can love the dead.
如果她离开
If she had only walked away,
我们就不会有这遭状况
we wouldn't be in this mess right now.
该死的吸血鬼婊子
Fucking vampire whore.
岔开大腿…
Spread your legs...
你说你是对的  可你看现在
You said you've been right. Look what it got you.
你怎么还活着  我宝贝却死了？
How come you're still alive and my baby's dead?
她就站在Terry的葬礼
She stood there at Terry's funeral
说一切真他妈操蛋
sayin' all this bullshit.
灭了那该死的吸血鬼
Exterminate the fuckin' vampires.
哈喽？
Hello?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
受伤了吗？
Are you hurt?
不  我很好
No, I'm okay.
Jess  他们杀了Tara
Jess, they-- they killed Tara.
恩  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我难以相信
I can't believe it.
等等  你在哪儿？
Wait, where are you?
额
Um...
在Bellefleur这里
I'm at the Bellefleurs'.
我为他们提供保护
I offered them my protection.
我得保护Adilyn
I'm going to protect Adilyn.
你进食了吗？
Have you fed?
我没事  我…我不饿
It's okay, I'm-- I'm not hungry.
Jess 你得进食
Jess, you have to eat.
我  等会儿见  好吗？
I-- I'll see you later, okay?
恩  好
Yeah, okay.
你是只狗
You're a dog.
什么？
What?
我看到了
I just saw you.
你刚是狗  你变回来的
You were a dog, you turned back into you.
那他妈是咋回事儿？
What the fuck was that about?
听着Vince  Norris市长同意的时候
Look, Vince, when Mayor Norris passed,
你我可是经过一场激烈论辩的
you and me fought a hard campaign against each other,
所以我不怪你吃不到葡萄说葡萄酸
so I don't blame you for sour grapes,
但你要告诉这些人我是只狗？
but you tell these people their mayor's a dog?
听着  这只会让他们觉得你是疯了
See, all that's gonna do is make you look crazy.
别说我看到的啥都不是
Don't tell me I didn't see what I saw.
你他妈就是只狗
You were a motherfucking dog.
我了个去  好好  你看到的没错
God damn it, fine. All right, you saw what you saw.
看看四周  Vince
Take a look around this place, Vince.
这儿的人几乎坚持不下去了
Folks here are barely holding on.
我们再扔一个炸弹  人们会更恐慌
We throw them another curveball, people are gonna panic.
那你他妈到底是啥？
What the fuck are you?
我会告诉你一切
I'll tell you everything,
Vince  但我们得先度过此关
Vince, but not until we get through this.
为这个你我都爱的小镇
For the sake of the town we both love,
我请求你  拜托了
I am begging you, please,
能先你我两人保密吗？
can we keep this between us just for now?
拜托？
Please?
嘿  听着各位
Hey, listen up, everybody.
这儿不安全
It's not safe here.
那些病毒吸血鬼们随时可能回来
Those Hep-V vamps could be back any time.
我们得让吸血鬼带领他们指定的人类
We need every vampire to take their assigned human
安全的回到他们的家
back to the safety of their home.
还有  如果每个反抗病毒吸血鬼的人类
And there, if every Hep-V negative human
为他们的吸血鬼提供给养
would kindly feed their vampire
换取他们的保护
in exchange for their protection,
那我们就有机会挺到明早
we got a better chance of making it through till the morning.
明早
Now, tomorrow morning,
我们在Daniel牧师教堂见
we're gonna meet up at Reverend Daniels' church
试着找出方法帮助人们
to try and figure out how to help those folks
避免伤害  请相互告知
who've been hit, so please spread the word.
你的人类呢？
You have a human?
过来  我带你回家
Come on. I'm gonna get you home.
我们回家  市长先生
Let's get you home, Mr. Mayor.
不  谢了老兄  我没事
No, thanks, man, I'm fine.
一人一鬼  这是你说的
Every vampire a human. This was your plan.
人们得看到你也是这样
People need to see you sticking to it.
好吧
All right.
嘿  我是Sookie
Hey, this is Sookie.
我现在不在  请留言
I'm not in right now. Please leave a message.
嘿  你去哪儿了？我在找你
Hey, where'd you go? I'm looking for you.
我们该回去了
We should head back.
来看“猎鹿人”了
We watch "Deer Hunter."
猎鹿人：电影  这里指打枪游戏
- 你叫什么？  - 滚你丫
- What is your name? - Go fuck yourself.
滚你丫小姐
The lady "Go Fuck Yourself"!
挑战者优先
Challenger go first.
我幸存了27次
I've survived 27 times.
27.
28次
28.
真主阿拉爱我呢
Allah loves me.
你的上帝爱你吗？
Does your god love you?
不  我的上帝恨死我了
Nope, my god fuckin' hates me.
世界正在走向灭亡
The world is ending.
你需要和你的上帝和平共处
You need to make peace with your god.
我爱的人都走了  我接触的人都死了
Everyone I love leaves, everything I touch dies,
所以如果我不和上帝说你的信仰  请原谅我
so forgive me if I don't share your faith in my Lord.
- 他能拯救你  - 恩  告诉你
- He can save you. - Yeah, tell you what.
我不管你我的上帝什么
Your god and my god can go to a motel
哪怕在他们在旅馆瞎搞
and have a circle jerk for all I care.
我也只是在地狱和恶魔交易
I'll be in Hell having a three-way with the Devil.
辞藻空洞
Your words are hollow.
我能看到你眼中的爱与痛
I can see the love and pain in your eyes.
因为这种感觉…
Because this feeling...
让你此时此刻接近上帝  不是吗
right now makes you closer to God, no?
让你知道你还活着？
Makes you know you're alive?
你死定了
You're dead.
不  我不会
No, I'm not.
我还活着
I'm alive.
所以我的制造者在哪儿？
So where the fuck's my maker?
你得去见这个人
This is who you have to see.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
很抱歉你朋友
I'm sorry about your friend.
谢了
Thanks.
就算窗户开着
You can't come in here, though, right?
- 你也不能进来  是吗？  - 对
- Even though the window's open? - That's right.
没有你的邀请我无法进入
I can't come in without an invitation.
这规定真奇怪
That's kind of a weird rule.
恩
Yeah.
我听到了你之前对我爸爸说的
I heard what you said to my dad before.
说你不想伤害我
About not wanting to hurt me.
我是说
I meant it.
我会做关于那晚的噩梦
I have nightmares about that night.
我也是
Me, too.
是因为我的血  是吗？
It's 'cause of my blood, right?
对吸血鬼来说我闻起来不同？
I smell different to vampires?
恩
Yes.
对你我还是很好闻吗？
Do I still smell good to you?
是
Yes.
你会杀了我吗？
Are you gonna kill me?
不会
No.
好  那你要是控制不住呢？
Well, what if you can't help it?
我应该恨你的
I should hate you.
但我没有
But I don't.
那是你男友吗？
Was that your boyfriend?
什么？
What?
电话里  是你男友吗？
On the phone, was that your boyfriend?
哦  恩  是
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
他长什么样子？
Well, what's he like?
他…他很可爱
He's-- he's so loving
有几分绅士
and kind and gentle
还很性感
and he's hot, too.
恩  他  真的很性感
Yeah, he's, like, sexy as heck.
你有男友吗？
Do you have a boyfriend?
有那么个男孩  我也说不准
There's this one boy, but I don't know.
他叫什么？
What's his name?
Wade
Wade.
Holly的孩子？
Holly's boy?
你迷恋Holly的儿子？
You have a crush on Holly's boy?
- 不  不算迷恋  - 是  你就是
- No, not a crush exactly. - Yes, you do.
她是谁？
What is she?
她是我的
She's mine.
你独自回家了
You walked home alone.
经过今晚发生的
After what happened tonight,
那些在树林里寻觅我们的
it ain't a question of whether these Hep-V vamps
病毒吸血鬼们都不是事儿了
are out there in the woods looking for us.
我们都知道他们就在外边Sookie
We know they're out there, Sookie.
你为什么还这样做？
Why would you do that?
- 我读了你的思想  - 什么？
- I read your thoughts. - What?
我很抱歉  我知道我不应该
I'm sorry, I know I'm not supposed to,
但是我今晚没有缓冲
but I got no buffer tonight.
- 我也不想...它们就这么跑脑子里... - Sookie
- And I can't-- they just keep coming in... - Sookie.
我觉得其他人都有可能这样想
...and I expect it from everybody else,
- 但是你不会的 - 什么？
- but not from you. - What?
你应该爱我  并且支持我
You're supposed to love me and support me,
但是即使是你也因为这个在怪我
and even you are blaming me for this,
为了这个小镇所发生的事情责怪我
blaming me for what's happened to this town
把Arlene的失踪也怪到我头上
and blaming me for Arlene being missing.
不  我没有
No, I'm not.
我能听到你的想法
I read your thoughts.
- Sookie  这不公平 - 我知道
- Sookie, it ain't fair. - I know that.
这样带有色眼镜看我
It ain't fair to judge me
并且把我拒之门外
and push me away
就因为我内心的一些想法
'cause of something I thought.
你的想法我都知道
I know that, too.
我爱你
I love you.
你并没有告诉我任何新鲜事
You're not telling me anything I don't already know
因为  还记得么
because, newsflash,
我他妈可以读懂你的想法
I can read your fucking thoughts,
你明白了？
you get it?
我很抱歉  这就是我身上该死的诅咒
I'm sorry, it's my fucking curse
总能知道别人对我的真实想法是怎样的
to know the truth of what people think of me always,
能够感觉到丑恶现实的
to feel the pain and the hurt
痛与伤
and the ugly, ugly truth.
即使是你  即使是Jason  即使是Andy和Sam
Even you, even Jason, even Andy and Sam
还有这个镇子上每一个该死的人类
and every goddamn human in this town.
- Sookie - Tara已经死了
- Sookie, I-- - Tara's dead.
我知道
I know.
- 我很抱歉 - 不  我才应该说抱歉
- I'm sorry. - No, I'm sorry.
我想一个人静一静
I need to be on my own right now.
好
Okay.
你见过多少次人死的场景了？
How many people you seen die?
多少？
How many?
数不清了
I've lost count.
你知道  我和Tara  我们一起长大的
You know, me and Tara, we grew up together.
她总经常来我家
She'd come over to our place all the time.
每次他妈妈一开始酗酒
She'd come running over
她就用她那对小细腿
with her skinny little legs
跑来我家
whenever her mom would hit the bottle.
这很奇怪  是不？
It's weird, huh?
我的意思是我感觉我们应该停下来了  是不是？
I mean, it feels like we should stop, don't it?
Jason
Jason.
什么？
What?
有人来过了
Somebody's here already.
怎么可能？
The hell?
晚上好  Stackhouse
Evening, Stackhouse.
Vince？
Vince?
你们来做什么？
What are you folks up to?
来杀掉那些感染病毒的吸血鬼
Hunting those H-vamps.
他们带走了Lou的兄弟
They took Lou's brother.
不是我有意冒犯  这好像是我的工作
All due respect, that's my job.
我也不是有意冒犯  你都没有装备
All due respect, you aren't equipped.
现在  联邦政府可能有
Now, the Feds might be,
但是他们都在大城市里安营扎寨
but they're all camped out in the big cities,
也就是说我们这种美国小镇
which means Small Town America, well,
只能靠自己了
we're on our own.
哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
听着 我们都很害怕
Listen, we are all freaked out
现在这种世界末日的情景
by the Armageddon-like situation that we got going on here,
但是你们准备自力更生？
but you folks taking matters into your own hands?
恩  那可能会死的更快
Well, that's just a shortcut straight to the morgue.
所以怎样? Jason？
So the alternative is to, what, Jason?
让我们相信你？
Put our faith in you?
或者Belledleur警长和Merlotte市长？
Or Sheriff Bellefleur and Mayor Merlotte?
如果是他们带走了Caleb
If they took Caleb,
我们会把他们抓回来的
we gotta get 'em back.
我要是你我就好好地把枪放下
I would seriously put that gun down if I were you.
- Violet 我能控制住  - 哦 这就完啦？
- Violet, I got this. - Oh, so is that how it is?
她现在就是法律了？吸血鬼警长？
Is she the law now? Deputy vampire?
不  这不是这样的
No, that's not how it is.
你也成吸血鬼脑残粉了  Stackhouse？
You a fangbanger now, Stackhouse?
- Jason是我的 - Violet
- Jason is mine. - Violet.
那你为什么不带着你那一丁丁点的小枪回家
So why don't you take your puny little guns back home
用你那可怜的小玩意儿
and go fuck your depressed homey housewives
去干你那个绝望的宅家老婆呢
with your tiny little dicks?
如果我没有屌呢？能留下么？
What if I don't have a dick? Can I stay?
那当然
Of course you can.
但是那时候我别无选择
But then I'll have no choice
只能把你的头揪下来
but to rip your fucking head off
- 放在桌上装糖果了 - Violet！
- and use it as a candy dish. - Violet!
好吧  现在
Okay, now,
你们这些人为什么不继续你们的呢？
why don't you folks go on, now?
好吧
All right.
好的  我们走
All right, come on.
那算什么？
What was that?
什么？
What?
哦  你可以进来  我猜
Oh, you can come in, I guess.
我喜欢你家
I like your place.
恩 这有点…我不知道怎么说…
Yeah, it has a certain ghetto je ne sais quoi.
我知道你得吃东西 但是…
I know you got to eat, but...
我他妈必须
it is motherfucking mandatory
现在把思绪拉离这里
that I get my brain
就他妈现在
out of this plane of existence right the fuck now.
所以给我一点时间让我转换一下
So gimme a sec while I get altered
之后就给你吃午饭
and then I'll give you lunch.
我可以也来点儿吗？
Can I?
所以  你是Jessica的男人  是么？
So, you Jessica's man, right?
是的
Yep.
她很酷
She cool.
我很抱歉你的表妹死了
I am sorry about your cousin.
你明白的  我觉得终于可以放松了
You know, I feel relieved.
我他妈是多变态？
How fucked up is that?
我猜是因为她第一次死的时候
I guess because I grieved the first time
我已经默哀过了
she died.
她第二次死  我都毫无感觉
The second time she died, I don't feel nothing inside.
我所有的朋友都死了…
All my friends died...
在越南
...in Vietnam.
所有的
All of them.
他们的尸体装在飞机上运回了家
Their bodies would be brought home on this plane.
木棺材  顶部有一面旗子
Wood coffins, a flag draped over top.
一名来通知的军官和教士
A notification officer and a chaplain
会出现在镇子里
would show up in town.
然后他们开着福特银河车沿路走下去
And they'd drive down the road in their Ford Galaxy
所有的爸爸妈妈
and all the moms and all the dads
都会来到前门
would come out on their front porch
他们屏住呼吸  等待着
and they would hold their breath and wait
看军官会在哪幢房子前停下
to see which house the officer stopped at.
你服过兵役？
You served?
我是个逃兵  反战论者
I was a draft dodger, a pacifist.
我不相信任何形式的暴力
I don't believe in violence in any form.
如果我生活在那时候
If I had lived then,
我肯定会支持你
I'd be right there with you.
有一天  我回家过圣诞节
One day, I was home for Christmas
军官来到了我最好朋友的家
and the officer came to my best friend's house.
Danny Monoghan 他就住在对面
Danny Monoghan. He lived right across the street.
Danny和我 我们…
Danny and I, we were--
恩 他曾经…
well, he was...
军官说Danny已经死了
The officer delivered the news that Danny had died
在Huemorta战役的时候
during the Battle of Hue-- mortar attack.
然后我跑过街
So I went across the street
向Danny家表示哀悼
to pay my respects to Danny's family.
Danny的父亲 Monoghan先生
Danny's dad, Mr. Monoghan,
他拿过Danny的旧棒球棒
he grabbed Danny's old Louisville Slugger.
整个高中那时候
It's the same bat Danny and I
我和Danny一人一根
had used all through high school.
他就在街中间狠狠滴打了我一顿
And he beat me with it right in the middle of the street.
该死
Fuck.
说我是“嬉皮基佬”
Called me a "Hippie faggot"
然后丢我在那里等死
And just left me there to die.
这个镇上的吸血鬼可怜我...
This vampire in town took pity on me...
那个晚上把我变成了吸血鬼
made me a vampire that night.
所以  如果你问我
So, if you ask me,
感到痛苦或者恐惧
there's zero point in feeling pain or fear,
悲痛或者是懊悔 都是没用的
grief or regret.
你可以笑  可以哭
You can laugh, you can cry,
你可以勃然大怒
you can smoke out.
这都无所谓
It doesn't matter.
对于Tara和宇宙
To Tara or to the universe.
这些都不会产生任何不同
It makes no fucking difference.
你就是一个形而上学的混蛋
You are one metaphysical fuck.
那么  小伙伴
So, homey.
让我看看你能做到什么
Gimme your best shot.
怎么这样？！
What the fuck?!
回到车上去
Get back in the car.
这里不安全 你在做什么呢？
It's not safe out here. What are you doing?
我是个男人
I am a man.
我他妈还是个警官
I'm a fucking officer of the law.
你就让我站在里面
You left me standing
我的屌却还在外面
with my dick out back there.
你让我怎么想？
How do you think that makes me feel?
我不知道 Jason
I don't know, Jason.
那让你感觉如何？
How does that make you feel?
你不让我操你
You won't let me fuck you.
你不让我做我的本职工作
You won't let me do my job.
你他妈每晚吸我的血
You fucking feed on me every night.
这都是扯淡！
This is bullshit!
我快憋死了
My balls are so fucking blue,
我的蛋蛋都快憋掉了
they're about to fall off.
恩  那你要怎么做呢
Well, what are you going to do about it,
哈 Jason？
huh, Jason?
我要操你
I'm gonna fuck you.
然后你也要迎合我
And you're gonna fuck me back.
我们要一起啪啪啪
We're gonna fuck together.
你听到我说的了吗  妹子？
You hear me, woman?
我们动起来！ 为操而操！
Let's fuck! For fuck's sake!
时间差不多到了 Jason
It's about fucking time, Jason.
我一直在等待
I've been waiting.
来吧 我的宝贝妹子！
Come on out, baby girl!
- 我不咬人！ - 他妈给我闭嘴！
- I don't bite! - Shut the fuck up!
为什么她闻起来这么香？
Why she smell so good?
你尝过？
You had a taste?
我理解你想把她据为己有
I get that you wanna keep her all to yourself.
把你的尖牙浸入她甜美的肉里
Sink your teeth into that sweet flesh.
但是你妈妈没教过你好东西要一起分享么？
But didn't your mama tell you it's nice to share?
你越过这里  我发誓我他妈一定杀了你！
You cross that line and I will fucking kill you!
我？
Me?
反正我也要死了
I'm dying anyway.
没什么可以失去的了
Got nothing to lose.
- 快关窗！ - 他不能伤害我的 你说过的
- Close the window! - He can't hurt me, you said.
只要我不邀请他进来
Not if I don't invite him in.
我说了他不能进来
I said that he couldn't come inside.
我从来没有说过他不会伤害你
I never said that he couldn't hurt you.
我们可以分享她  我们可以操她
We could share her. We could fuck her.
- 我需要你喝我的血 - 什么？
- I need you to drink my blood. - What?
听着  如果你喝了我的血  即使只有一滴
Listen, if you drink my blood, even one drop,
我就总能感应到你在哪里
I will always know where you are
然后我就可以一直保护你了
and I will always be able to protect you.
好么？
Okay?
不
No.
你必须得相信我
You're gonna have to trust me.
我曾经相信过你
I trusted you before.
你他妈给我退回去！
You stay the fuck back!
我要在死之前尝尝这个小女孩
I'm gonna taste that little girl before I die.
哦 亲爱的上帝 我能看到她
Oh, sweet Jesus. I can see her.
甜心 没事的
Honey, it's gonna be all right.
我的Tara在跟我说话
My Tara's talking to me.
Tara? Tara?
Tara? 宝贝？ 我在这里
Tara, baby? I'm right here.
她怎么了？
What's wrong with her?
- 她喝了你的血嗨了 - 我在这里 宝贝
- She's high on your blood. - I'm right here, baby.
我没有给她那么多啊
I didn't give her that much.
去另一边堵住她
Go around the other side.
Daniels夫人 你得冷静下来
Mrs. Daniels, you gotta calm down.
她不在天堂  她需要我们的帮忙
She ain't in Heaven. She needs our help.
那只是吸血鬼的血在替你说话
That's the vampire blood talking.
- 甜心  来吧  来吧 - 她不能说话
- Honey, come on, come on. - She can't speak.
- 听我说  - 她没有说话
- Listen to me. - She ain't saying any words.
Tara已经死了 你明白吗？
Tara is on the other side, you see?
- 她不在天堂 - 甜心 听我说
- She ain't in Heaven. - Honey, listen to me.
她需要我
She needs me.
不 不 你只是V血嗨了而已
No, no, that's the vampire blood talking now.
嘘  我想要你安静下来
Shh, I want you to quiet down.
就是这样  安静下来  现在  躺下
That's it, quiet down. Now, lay down.
- 躺下 - Tara 我就在这里
- Lay down. - Tara, I'm right here.
Tara...
- 我就在这里 - 嘘
- I'm right here. - Shh.
- 睡吧 宝贝 睡吧 - 我不会离开你的
- Go to sleep, baby. Go to sleep. - I won't leave you.
嘘
Shh.
- 我不会 我不会的 - 是的 是的
- I won't. I won't. - Yes, yes.
- 我不会 我不会的 - 是的
- I won't. I won't. - Yes.
Tara跟你提过她…
Tara ever tell you about her--
她妈妈的问题吗？
her mother's issues?
我略知一二
I know a little bit.
不要再给她任何血了  你明白么？
No more blood for her, you understand?
当然
Of course.
明早之前就能排出体外了
It'll be out of her system by morning.
谢谢你来帮忙
Thank you for your help.
我无处可去
I've got nowhere to go.
Eric已经走了
Eric's gone.
Pam也不见了
Pam's gone.
我本来和Tara住一起的  但是我...
And I was rooming with Tara, but I--
我回不去了
I can't go back there.
我无法谁在那里
I can't sleep there
四周都是她的东西  她的气息
with all of her stuff and her smell
但是她却…不在了
with her just being... gone.
上帝啊 上帝啊 上帝啊
Lord, Lord, Lord.
你这头迷失的小绵羊 是不是？
You a lost sheep, ain't ya?
跟我来
Come with me.
上帝知道这间房不咋地...
Lord knows it ain't much...
但是它密不透光
but it's light-tight.
你可以在这里想呆多久都可以
You can stay as long as you'd like.
明晚见
I'll see you tomorrow night.
你先睡吧  甜心
You sleep now, sweetheart.
谢谢
Thank you.
Sami
Sami.
我的女儿给你
My daughter for you.
她没病
She is no sick.
恩 你的女儿看起来很可口
While your daughter does look delicious,
但是我不能接受
I'll pass.
你上一次吸血是什么时候？
When was last time you feed?
我没事的
I'll be fine.
我就是需要那条讯息 拜托了
Just the information, please.
这里肯定有什么错误
There must be some mistake.
没有错误
No mistake.
- 他绝不会 - 我的信息是准确的
- He would never-- - My information is accurate.
你怎么做是你的选择
What you do is your choice.
嘿
Hey.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事
It's okay.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
这地方一年以前就关闭了
This place closed down a year ago.
原来经常看到小孩子来这里玩
Used to find kids partying in here all the time.
他们在这里安窝了
They've been nesting here.
Holly！
Holly!
神啊
Jesus Ch--
- 嘿 嘿！ - 别动！
- Hey, hey! -  Don't move!
- 哇 哇 哇  - 吸血鬼！
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! - Vampire!
等一下  等一下
Hold on, hold on.
好好待着别动 Compton先生
Stay right where you are Mr. Compton.
发生了什么事情？
What seems to be the problem?
别看他的眼睛  大家
Don't look him in the eyes, y'all.
好的  大家都冷静下来  好么？
All right, everybody calm down, all right?
我们都是一边的
We're all on the same side here.
一边个鬼  他们抓走了我兄弟
Like fuck we are. They took my brother.
他们抓走了Holly
They took my Holly.
恩  一报还一报
Well, then it serves you right.
是的
Yeah.
一人给养一个吸血鬼
"For every human a vampire"?
一个吸血鬼保护一个人？
"For every vampire a human"?
看看他们对人类都做了什么
Look at what they're doing to people.
你和Merlotte市长
You and Mayor Merlotte,
站在教堂里
you stood up there in church
告诉我们要相信吸血鬼
and you told us to trust the vampires.
现在我们爱着的人死了！
Now people we love are dead!
朋友被挟走了！
Our friends have been taken!
你要的是我
It's me that you want.
搭伴儿也是我的主意
The mixer was my idea.
- 我和Merlotte市长的  - 他不是我市长
- Mine and Mayor Merlotte's. - He ain't my mayor.
现在你也许没有注意
Now maybe you didn't notice,
但今晚警探不在Bellefleur那里
but the sheriff wasn't at Bellefleur's tonight.
知道给他打电话说发生了什么
Not until he got the call about what happened.
他都在家表示抗议
He was at home in protest.
让他走
You let him go,
你怎么处置我都行
you can do what you want with me.
那好吧
All right, then.
你走吧  Andy
Why don't you get outta here, Andy?
别回头看
And don't look back 'cause
你不会想看下一幕的
you don't wanna see what's coming next.
哇哦  那你就错了
Well, that's where you're wrong.
我还真想看
I do wanna see it.
这个吸血鬼和我
This vampire and me,
还有一段糟糕的历史的
there's a history here and it ain't a good one.
如果你要了结了他
If you're gonna end him,
我愿意帮你
I deserve to be the one to do it.
他对你做了什么？
What'd he do to you?
那是我和他的事
That's between him and me.
好吧  警探  那你来
Okay, Sheriff, do it.
你可以站在我们这边
We could use you on our side.
我们这边儿需要你
Andy
Andy!
你叫什么  孩子？
What's your name, son?
- Lou  - 听我说  Luo
- Lou. - Listen to me, Lou.
我想你在这一刻
I want you to forget the fact that I'm the sheriff
忘记我是这个教区的警探
of this parish for just a second.
用枪指着人真可谓是个大交易
Firing a weapon at another human being is a big fucking deal.
一旦做了  扣动扳机
When you do it, when you pull that trigger,
你就再也没有回头路了
you are crossing a line you can never come back from.
放下它
Pull it.
你的人生就不一样了
Your life's never gonna be the same.
你确定这是你想要的
You be sure this is what you wanna do
因为我会扣下我的扳机  Luo
'cause I will pull my fucking trigger, Lou.
我会打一枪  然后再补一枪
I've done it before and I'll do it again.
天啊  我真会的
So help me, God, I will.
所以快离开这儿
Get the hell outta here.
走吧  回家  这儿不安全
Go on, go home. It's not safe.
我真不敢相信你刚的选择
I can't believe you're just gonna stand by
你让这吸血鬼血洗小镇
and let these H-vamps kill our town.
我哪边也不选
Ain't nobody standin' by.
事态还会继续的
It's to be continued.
不  孩子  这儿的该结束了
No, son, this shit's over.
走！
Get!
来吧  伙计  这家伙估计喝多了
Come on. Man, he's drunk anyway.
上帝啊！
Jesus Christ!
我们永远出不去了
We ain't never gonna make it outta here.
永远
Not ever.
良辰镇就一个五人警队
Bon Temps got a police force of five people
我是其中之一
and I'm one of them.
这不是真的  Andy会找到我们的
That is not true. Andy's gonna find us.
我们在什里夫波特！
We are in Shreveport!
什里夫波特：美国路易斯安那州西北部城市
吸血鬼酒吧的地下室！
In the basement of some fangbanger bar!
他们能及时找到我们吗？
How they gonna find us in time?
哦  天啊
Oh, my God!
我不能死这儿  我还有孩子啊
I can't die down here. I've got kids.
不不不  保持清醒  Arlene
No, no, no, no. You've gotta keep your head up, Arlene.
听到没？
You hear me?
我不许在我面前胡思乱想
I can't have you losing it on me.
嘿  嘿  会没事的
Hey, hey, hey, it's gonna be okay.
- 我们会没事的  - 我感觉不到她了
- We're gonna be okay. - I can't feel her.
我不认为她…
I don't think she's--
她会没事的  她很好
She's gonna be okay. She's just fine.
哦  天啊
Oh, God!
低下头  保持安静
Keep your head down and be quiet.
我们都会死的
We're all gonna die.
哦  天啊  哦  天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
拜托  上帝  求你了
Oh, please, God. Please.
上帝啊  不要  求你  求求你了
Oh, God, please don't. Please, please.
哦不  哦  不
Oh, no. Oh, no.
哦  不
Oh, no.
求你  不要  不要
Please, please, don't. Please,
求你  别杀我
please, please, don't kill me.
求你  求你  求求你
Please, please, please.
求你  求你  不要  不要杀我
Oh, please, please don't. Please don't.
哦  天啊
Oh, God.
哦  不  不
Oh, no. No.
想都别想
No fucking way.
哦  不
Oh, no.
你不必这样的
You don't have to do this.
听着  刚的事情  我想说谢谢
Look, I wanna say thank you for what you did back there.
我刚之所以救你是需要你帮我
I saved your miserable hide because I need your help
救回Holly和Arlene
to get Holly and Arlene back.
这不代表我们友好
But we are not good.
我们也绝不会友好
We will never be good.
这世界上也没有什么东西可以弥补
There ain't nothing in this world can make right
你对我及我家人的所作所为
what you done to me and my family.
所以省省你的谢谢
So save your thanks.
再见  爸爸
Bye, Daddy.
黎明来了  你该走了
Dawn's coming. You should go.
你愿为她而死吗？
You're willing to die for her?
我不会离开的
I am not leaving.
我们有个阁楼！
We have an attic!
不！
No!
你在外边会死的！
You're gonna die out here!
呆在屋里  别邀请我
You stay inside. Do not invite me in.
我相信你
I trust you.
你不应该相信
You shouldn't.
Jessica  我邀请你进来
Jessica, I invite you in.
我擦
Fuck.
我邀请你进来！
I invite you in!
不不
No! No!
让我进来  你个贱婊子！
Let me in, you fucking bitch!
让我进去！
Let me in!
来吧  小妞
Come on, lady!
她是我的啊
I've gotta make her mine!
让我进去！
Let me in!
你个婊子！
You bitch!
不不不
No! No! No!
是的  兄弟姐妹们  昨晚
Yes, brothers and sisters, it has been night
长夜难熬
a long, long time.
但我今晨醒来  向上帝祷告
But when I got up today, I prayed to God.
请求他的指引
I asked Him for guidance.
我倾心聆听
I strained to listen.
他告诉我
And He told me,
“清晨已至”
"Morning is coming."
是的  他说的对  清晨已至
Yes, He did. Morning is coming.
- 我们一起说  阿门  - 阿门
- Let the church say, "Amen." - All: Amen.
你们需要相信我  上帝之子
You have to believe me, children of God,
如果你还和上帝同在
that when you stay with the Lord,
亲附他
if you cling to Him,
如果你还坚守他
if you abide in Him,
那么  那会让你抓住清晨一瞥
well, then, He'll let you catch a glimpse of the morning.
很难再说什么
It's hard to know what to say.
我们的社区遭遇袭击
Our community has been raided.
别把手放我肩上  Sookie Stackhouse
Don't you put your hand on me, Sookie Stackhouse.
我宝贝的死都是你的错
It's your fault my baby's dead.
她总是会追随你
She always went running to you.
你却让她倒下了
And you led her down the path to Hell.
这上帝之所不欢迎你
You are not welcome in this house of God.
无耻荡妇
Fucking slut.
麻痹吸血鬼淫妇
Vampire-fucking bitch.
为什么不跑向你那鬼情人？
Why don't you run back to your vampire lover?
- 操你丫的  荡妇  - 她不觉得无耻吗？
- I wanna fuck you, vampire fucker. - Has she no shame?
- 滚出去  傻蛋  - 真希望她离开
- Get out, you stupid cunt. - I wish she would leave.
- 捅你妹啊  - 草泥马该死的
- Vampires flock to you like geese. - I'm wanna fuckin' kill you.
- 还得待多久啊？ - 伤透了心
- How long can I stay off? - Stab you through the heart.
你快离开小镇吧  你不属于这儿
Run you out of town. You don't belong here.
我能听到你们说的
I can hear you.
你们每个人说的我都能听到
I can hear each and every one of you.
至少Lettie Mae会体面的说
At least Lettie Mae's got the decency
她对我的看法
to say what she thinks to my face.
我一生都居住在良辰镇
I've lived in Bon Temps my whole life.
我爱这小镇
And I love this town,
我这一生也都在聆听你们
and I've known all of you my whole life.
就算你们大部分都恨我
And even though most of you hate me,
可我就是爱你们每个人
I love just about everybody here.
我知道你们大部分人怎么看我
And I know what most of you think of me,
一些人把发生的事归罪于我
that some of you blame me for what's happened.
这不错
And you're not wrong.
我是原因之一
I played a part,
但事情回不到从前
but we can't go back to the way things were
我也无法拯救那些失去的人
and I can't save those who have been lost.
但我们的一些朋友  爱人
But some of our friends and loved ones
正在为活着的人奋战
are fighting for their lives right now,
不管好坏
and for better or for worse,
这小镇没人比我更了解吸血鬼
nobody in this town knows vampires better than me.
我想帮忙
I wanna help.
请让我帮忙
Please let me help.
真 爱 字 幕 组
出  品